Brother Yuanqi,
الأخ يوانكي
All these years of feelings between us,
كل هذه السنوات من المشاعر بيننا،
You have always been in my heart.
لقد كنت دائما في قلبي.
Please forgive me this time.
أرجوك أن تسامحني هذه المرة.
As long as you forgive me,
طالما أنك تسامحني،
I'll do anything you ask.
سأفعل أي شيء تطلبه.
I can offer myself
أستطيع أن أعرض نفسي
to make amends to you.
لإصلاح لك.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Step aside!
تنحى!
Shameless!
وقح!
How disgusting can you be?
هل يمكنك أن تكون مقززًا؟
Brother Yuanqi,
الأخ يوانكي
You worked to support my studies.
لقد عملت على دعم دراستي.
You care about me, don't you?
أنت تهتم بي، أليس كذلك؟
You've endured so much hardship.
لقد تحملت الكثير من المشقة.
Please forgive me just this once.
أرجوك أن تسامحني هذه المرة فقط.
I'm begging you.
انا أتوسل إليك.
I promise I'll listen to you in everything from now on.
أعدك بأنني سأستمع إليك في كل شيء من الآن فصاعدا.
Xiao Yanzhi.
شياو يانزي.
Let me tell you,
دعني أخبرك،
everything in the past
كل شيء في الماضي
is irreversible.
لا رجعة فيه.
The Chen Yuanqi who cared for you is gone.
لقد رحل تشين يوانكي الذي كان يهتم بك.
I'll tell you one last time.
سأخبرك للمرة الأخيرة.
From now on, I never want to see you again.
من الآن فصاعدا، لا أريد رؤيتك مرة أخرى.
Do you understand?
هل تفهم؟
Get out.
اخرج.
Leave.
يترك.
Why are you still here?
لماذا مازلت هنا؟
Senior Sister.
الأخت الكبرى.
I came to bring you some pills.
لقد جئت لأحضر لك بعض الحبوب.
These pills can help you strengthen your cultivation.
يمكن لهذه الحبوب أن تساعدك على تقوية زراعتك.
Focus your mind and return to your origin.
ركز عقلك و عد إلى أصلك.
Thank you, Senior Sister.
شكرا لك أختي الكبرى.
You...
أنت...
When did you get here?
متى وصلت هنا؟
I...
أنا...
Since she arrived.
منذ وصولها.
I've been here.
لقد كنت هنا.
Ah...
اه...
I...
أنا...
Sorry, Senior Sister.
عذرا أختي الكبرى.
I made a fool of myself.
لقد جعلت من نفسي أضحوكة.
It's fine.
إنه بخير.
You...
أنت...
You're not as...
أنت لست مثل...
...lustful as I thought.
... شهواني كما اعتقدت.
Senior Sister, why would you think that of me?
الأخت الكبرى لماذا تعتقدين ذلك عني؟
Because back in the cave, you...
لأنه في الكهف مرة أخرى، أنت...
...toward me...
... نحوي...
That was...
كان ذلك...
...like that.
...مثل ذلك.
The cave...
الكهف...
That was because of you in the cave.
وكان ذلك بسببك في الكهف.
Last time was because—Enough!
المرة الأخيرة كانت بسبب-كفى!
Don't bring it up again.
لا تذكر هذا الموضوع مرة أخرى.
Yes, as you wish.
نعم كما تريد.
I won't mention it.
لن أذكر ذلك.
Don't misunderstand.
لا تسيء الفهم.
I just don't want to owe you a favor.
أنا فقط لا أريد أن أدين لك بمعروف.
Yes, yes, no favors owed.
نعم، نعم، لا يوجد أي مقابل.
No more debts.
لا مزيد من الديون.
Also...
أيضًا...
I think...
أظن...
You're pretty good.
أنت جيد جدًا.
I'm pretty good?
هل أنا جيد جدًا؟
Why do you keep repeating what I say?
لماذا تستمر في تكرار ما أقوله؟
Are you stupid?
هل انت غبي؟
I...
أنا...
Anyway...
على أي حال...
Thank you for saving me again today.
شكرا لك على إنقاذي مرة أخرى اليوم.
I'm leaving.
انا ذاهب.
Good luck in tomorrow's tournament.
حظا سعيدا في بطولة الغد.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
You...
أنت...
Today is the final of the Grand Competition at Tianyuan Academy.
اليوم هو نهائي المسابقة الكبرى في أكاديمية تيانيوان.
Between outer disciple Chen Yuanqi
بين التلميذ الخارجي تشين يوانكي
and inner disciple Fu Bing.
والتلميذ الداخلي فو بينج.
The winner
الفائز
will become my personal disciple.
سيصبح تلميذي الشخصي.
And the future successor of the sect master.
والخليفة المستقبلي لسيد الطائفة.
Everyone, please wait.
الجميع، الرجاء الانتظار.
Allow me to expose the true face of a wolf in sheep’s clothing.
اسمحوا لي أن أكشف الوجه الحقيقي للذئب في ثياب الحمل.
It is him.
إنه هو.
Chen Yuanqi.
تشن يوانكي.
He tried to assault me last night.
لقد حاول الاعتداء علي الليلة الماضية.
Now, relying on his strength,
الآن، بالاعتماد على قوته،
he acts as he pleases.
يتصرف كما يشاء
A person like this
شخص مثل هذا
is not qualified to compete in the Tianyuan Academy finals.
غير مؤهل للمنافسة في نهائيات أكاديمية تيانيوان.
You’re slandering me!
أنت تقذفني!
Here is the evidence.
وهنا الدليل.
You tried to assault me last night.
لقد حاولت الاعتداء علي الليلة الماضية.
I took your coin pouch before I escaped.
لقد أخذت حقيبة نقودك قبل أن أهرب.
Do you dare swear that this isn’t yours?
هل تجرؤ على أن تقسم أن هذا ليس لك؟
Xiao Yanzhi.
شياو يانزي.
Do you dare to swear?
هل تجرؤ على الشتم؟
Wasn’t it you who seduced me first last night?
ألم تكن أنت من أغويني أولاً الليلة الماضية؟
Of course I dare.
بالطبع أجرؤ.
If I shamelessly seduced you last night,
إذا أغويتك بلا خجل الليلة الماضية،
may I die a miserable death.
أتمنى أن أموت موتة بائسة.
Chen Yuanqi.
تشن يوانكي.
In truth, you and Xue Cheng are both Demonic Cultivators.
في الحقيقة، أنت و شيويه تشنغ كلاكما من المزارعين الشيطانيين.
Your power grew rapidly.
لقد زادت قوتك بسرعة.
But Xue Cheng lost control and went mad.
لكن شيو تشنغ فقد السيطرة وأصيب بالجنون.
Afraid your secret would be exposed,
خائف من أن يتم الكشف عن سرك،
you killed him to silence him.
قتلته لإسكاته.
I see now.
انا ارى الان.
Your spirit power is also in the Spirit Testing Stone.
قوتك الروحية موجودة أيضًا في حجر اختبار الروح.
There’s so much evil energy.
هناك الكثير من الطاقة الشريرة.
Who knows if it’s yours or his?
من يدري إن كان لك أو له؟
My cultivation,
زراعتي،
has nothing shameful about it.
ليس فيه شيء مخجل.
You practice demonic arts but won’t admit it.
أنت تمارس الفنون الشيطانية ولكنك لا تريد الاعتراف بذلك.
Shameless wretch!
أيها الوغد الوقح!
So Chen Yuanqi practices demonic arts.
لذلك يمارس تشين يوانكي الفنون الشيطانية.
No wonder he could win.
فلا عجب أنه يستطيع الفوز.
Everyone,
الجميع،
Chen Yuanqi does not cultivate demonic arts.
تشين يوانكي لا يزرع الفنون الشيطانية.
I can testify.
أستطيع أن أشهد.
Yesterday, when he healed me,
بالأمس، عندما شفاني،
his spirit power was pure and clear.
وكانت قوته الروحية نقية وواضحة.
There was no trace of evil.
لم يكن هناك أي أثر للشر.
But you,
ولكن انت
Fu Qingyun,
فو تشينغيون,
you and your brother Fu Bing
أنت وأخوك فو بينج
use the Fu family’s power
استخدم قوة عائلة فو
to bully Chen Yuanqi’s family.
لتخويف عائلة تشين يوانكي.
Jiang Yumeng, stop slandering us!
جيانغ يومينغ، توقف عن التشهير بنا!
Fu Qingyun,
فو تشينغيون,
you seized another man’s wife.
لقد استولت على زوجة رجل آخر.
Your brother killed someone’s mother.
أخوك قتل أم شخص ما.
Such beastly acts
مثل هذه الأعمال الوحشية
are unworthy of a noble family’s heir.
لا يستحقون أن يكونوا وريثًا لعائلة نبيلة.
You’re lying!
أنت تكذب!
I am not lying.
أنا لا أكذب.
I was there that day.
كنت هناك في ذلك اليوم.
I saw it with my own eyes.
لقد رأيته بأم عيني.
You were the masked woman who saved Chen Yuanqi that day.
لقد كنتِ المرأة المقنعة التي أنقذت تشين يوانكي في ذلك اليوم.
It was him! This beast did it!
لقد كان هو! هذا الوحش فعلها!
I never thought the Fu family would do such things.
لم أكن أتوقع أبدًا أن عائلة فو ستفعل مثل هذه الأشياء.
Beast! Shameless!
وحش! وقح!
Fu Bing.
فو بنج.
What kind of skill is it to bully women?
ما هي مهارة التنمر على النساء؟
Your opponent is me.
خصمك هو أنا.
If you want to silence someone,
إذا كنت تريد إسكات شخص ما،
you’ve picked the wrong person.
لقد اخترت الشخص الخطأ
You slandered my Fu family ancestors first.
لقد قمت بتشويه سمعة أسلافي من عائلة فو أولاً.
Why shouldn’t I strike back in anger?
لماذا لا أرد بالغضب؟
If you have the skill, face me on the stage.
إذا كانت لديك المهارة، واجهني على المسرح.
Fine!
بخير!
Let’s fight!
دعونا نقاتل!
I’ll go.
سأذهب.
Fu Bing.
فو بنج.
Where is my mother’s soul?
أين روح أمي؟
I don’t understand what you’re saying.
لا أفهم ما تقوله.
Fu Bing.
فو بنج.
Fight me!
قاتلني!
This aura...
هذه الهالة...
Chen Yuanqi’s cultivation
زراعة تشن يوانكي
is actually equal to Fu Bing’s.
هو في الواقع يساوي فو بينج.
How is this possible?
كيف هذا ممكن؟
Tianyuan Academy’s Cloud-Splitting Sword Qi!
سيف تشى لتقسيم السحاب من أكاديمية تيانيوان!
Cloud-Splitting Technique!
تقنية تقسيم السحابة!
That’s the most
هذا هو الأكثر
spirit-consuming technique in our sect.
تقنية استهلاك الروح في طائفتنا.
How can his spirit power be so abundant?
كيف يمكن لقوته الروحية أن تكون وفيرة إلى هذا الحد؟
He’s facing Fu Bing, the Qi-Dispersing Hand!
إنه يواجه فو بينج، اليد المشتتة للطاقة!
Right, when did his cultivation become so strong?
حسنًا، متى أصبحت زراعته قوية جدًا؟
All Qi Returns to Origin!
كل تشي يعود إلى أصله!
Eternal Phoenix Flame!
شعلة الفينيق الأبدية!
Brother,
أخ،
Hand over my mother's soul.
سلم روح أمي.
Scoundrel, don't be arrogant!
أيها الوغد، لا تكن مغرورًا!
With just a few of you,
مع عدد قليل منكم،
you think you can stop me?
هل تعتقد أنك تستطيع إيقافي؟
Give me back my mother's soul!
أعيدوا لي روح أمي!
Noble families
العائلات النبيلة
are not something a low-born sword servant like you can compare to.
ليسوا شيئًا يمكن لخادم السيف من أصل منخفض مثلك مقارنته به.
You want your mother's soul?
هل تريد روح والدتك؟
Keep dreaming.
استمر بالحلم.
Our clan elder, Fu Bufan,
شيخ عشيرتنا، فو بوفان،
has taken it to Beast God Forest for sacrifice.
أخذه إلى غابة إله الوحوش للتضحية به.
Even if I tell you,
حتى لو قلت لك،
what can you do about it?
ماذا يمكنك أن تفعل حيال ذلك؟
Bastard!
نذل!
I will make you pay in blood!
سأجعلك تدفع الثمن بالدم!
Brother,
أخ،
Chen Yuanqi has harmed his fellow disciples.
لقد أذى تشين يوانكي تلاميذه الآخرين.
His crime is unforgivable.
جريمته لا تغتفر.
He harmed my mother first.
لقد أذى والدتي أولاً.
Why shouldn't I kill him?
لماذا لا أقتله؟
Elders attacking a junior,
شيوخ يهاجمون صغارًا،
aren't you afraid of becoming a laughingstock?
ألا تخاف من أن تصبح أضحوكة؟
He killed my clan brother.
لقد قتل أخي من عشيرتي.
He must die today.
يجب أن يموت اليوم.
Yumeng, step aside!
يومينغ، تنحى جانبا!
Chen Yuanqi has harmed his fellow disciples.
لقد أذى تشين يوانكي تلاميذه الآخرين.
He deserves to pay with his life.
إنه يستحق أن يدفع حياته ثمنًا لذلك.
If you don't move,
إذا لم تتحرك،
you'll share his guilt.
سوف تشاركه ذنبه.
Senior Sister,
الأخت الكبرى،
Leave quickly.
إرحل بسرعة.
I don't want to drag you into this.
لا أريد أن أجرك إلى هذا.
I'll do as I please.
سأفعل ما يحلو لي.
Today,
اليوم،
I will stand up for him.
سأدافع عنه.
Senior Sister,
الأخت الكبرى،
Everyone,
الجميع،
why not see what I have in my hand?
لماذا لا أرى ما في يدي؟
Then decide if you want to fight me.
ثم قرر إذا كنت تريد قتالي.
This is from the Guanghan Jiang family.
هذا من عائلة قوانغهان جيانج.
A protective jade.
اليشم الواقي.
The supreme treasure of a top noble family.
الكنز الأعظم لعائلة نبيلة عليا.
Why do you have it?
لماذا لديك ذلك؟
Guanghan Heavenly River Water
مياه نهر قوانغهان السماوي
can overwhelm an entire sect.
يمكن أن تطغى على طائفة بأكملها.
Jiang Yumeng of the Guanghan Jiang clan is here.
جيانغ يومينغ من عشيرة Guanghan Jiang موجود هنا.
Miss Jiang,
السيدة جيانغ
Though the Guanghan clan is a top noble family,
على الرغم من أن عشيرة قوانغهان هي عائلة نبيلة عليا،
a mighty dragon can't suppress a local snake.
لا يستطيع التنين العظيم قمع ثعبان محلي.
In Chang'an, you don't need to risk conflict over this nobody.
في تشانغآن، لا داعي للمخاطرة بالصراع على هذا الشخص.
and make an enemy of the Fu family.
وجعل عدوًا لعائلة فو.
Become enemies?
أصبحوا أعداء؟
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
I am the direct descendant of the Guanghan Jiang clan.
أنا من نسل عشيرة قوانغهان جيانج المباشر.
Today,
اليوم،
anyone who harms Chen Yuanqi
أي شخص يؤذي تشين يوانكي
will be an enemy of the Guanghan Jiang clan.
سيكون عدوًا لعشيرة قوانغهان جيانج.
What? Direct descendant?
ماذا؟ سليل مباشر؟
I never expected that.
لم أتوقع ذلك أبدًا.
Our Tianyuan Academy
أكاديمية تيانيوان الخاصة بنا
actually has a Guanghan Jiang clan member studying here.
في الواقع يوجد عضو من عشيرة قوانغهان جيانج يدرس هنا.
It truly brings honor to our humble place.
إنه حقا يجلب الشرف لمكاننا المتواضع.
Yuanqi,
يوانكي،
why didn't you say so earlier?
لماذا لم تقل ذلك في وقت سابق؟
You have ties to the Guanghan Jiang clan.
لديك علاقات مع عشيرة قوانغهان جيانج.
I declare
انا أعلن
that in this martial tournament,
أنه في هذه البطولة القتالية،
Chen Yuanqi is the champion.
تشين يوانكي هو البطل.
From now on, he is my personal disciple.
ومن الآن فصاعدا، فهو تلميذي الشخصي.
Good, good, good!
جيد، جيد، جيد!
Fu Qingyun,
فو تشينغيون,
Where is my mother's soul in Beast God Forest?
أين روح أمي في غابة إله الوحوش؟
Beast God Forest stretches for thousands of miles.
تمتد غابة إله الوحوش لآلاف الأميال.
How would I know?
كيف سأعرف؟
Find it yourself.
ابحث عنه بنفسك.
You...
أنت...
The soul sacrifice technique
تقنية التضحية بالروح
is a secret art of the Hound Spirit Clan.
هو فن سري لعشيرة روح الكلب.
I know the Hound Spirit Clan
أنا أعرف عشيرة روح الكلب
has a place in Beast God Forest.
لديه مكان في غابة إله الوحوش.
Senior Sister,
الأخت الكبرى،
Thank you, Senior Sister.
شكرا لك أختي الكبرى.
Beast God Forest is full of dangers.
غابة إله الوحوش مليئة بالمخاطر.
You don't need to go with me.
لا تحتاج للذهاب معي.
How do you know Beast God Forest doesn't have what I need?
كيف تعرف أن غابة إله الوحوش لا تحتوي على ما أحتاجه؟
Yuanqi,
يوانكي،
I didn't expect you to rise to prominence.
لم أتوقع أنك سوف ترتفع إلى الشهرة.
I will make you return to me.
سأعيدك إليّ.
Let go of me!
أتركني!
With so much Hound Spirit Clan essence,
مع الكثير من جوهر عشيرة Hound Spirit،
I will surely succeed.
سوف أنجح بالتأكيد.
Absorbing our flesh and blood
امتصاص لحمنا ودمنا
to strengthen your cultivation,
لتعزيز زراعتك،
aren't you afraid of retribution?
ألا تخاف من الانتقام؟
Retribution?
القصاص؟
Let me show you what retribution is!
دعني أريك ما هو الانتقام!
No!
لا!